Finding Aid for Cornelia G. Kennedy papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Other Professional Organizations and Meetings 1968-2009
  - Moot Court Competitions at Law Schools
    - University of Michigan/Campbell and Harvard University/Ames 1973, 1976, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Notre Dame 1978, 1979, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Detroit and University of Illinois 1979, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Duke University 1980 (Box 42)
    - Washington and Lee University and University of Toledo 1981, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Akron and Northwestern University 1982, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Cleveland State University and Wayne State University 1984, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of California at Los Angeles 1984-1985 (Box 42)
    - University of Michigan, Ohio State University, and University of Colorado 1988, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Vanderbilt University 1990, 1991, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Iowa and Northwestern University 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Cornell University, Vanderbilt University, and Wake Forest University, NC 1991-1992, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Fordham University and Boston College 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Toledo, University of Tennessee 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Wayne State University and University of Michigan 1997-1998 (Box 42)
    - University of Cincinnati 1996, 1999 (Box 42)
    - University of Cincinnati, Cornell University, and University of Pennsylvania 2001-2002, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Cincinnati 2004-2005 (Box 42)
    - Michigan State University, College of William and Mary 2007, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - National Moot Court Competition, U.S. Courthouse, Detroit 1984 (Box 42)
  - U. S. Department of Justice, Office of Legal Education, Attorney General's Appellate Advocacy Institute
    - Appellate Advocacy Courses, including Moot Court Sessions
      - May, 1979 1981, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - May 14, Group Photograph, and November, 1982, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - May 27, June 8, and August 30, respectively 1983, 1984, 1985, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - November 18 and March 16-20, respectively 1988, 1992, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - March 5, 1993 September 3, 1993, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - March 1, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Joint Sentencing Institute, 6th and 9th Circuits 1975 (Box 42)
  - Conferences to Expedite Trials 1978, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - U.S. Parole Commission Hearings on Guideline Revision, Denver, Colorado Meeting 1978-1979 (Box 42)
  - Federal/State Judges' Ad Hoc Committee Meeting, Lansing 1980 (Box 42)
  - Eighth Economics Institute for Federal Judges, Law and Economics Center, University of Miami School of Law, Florida 1981 (Box 42)
  - Nashville Bar Association Meeting 1982 (Box 42)
  - Law and Economics Institute for Federal Judges, Emory University 1983 (Box 42)
  - Education and the Courts, Seminars for Federal Judges and Educators, Danforth Foundation, Colorado 1984 (Box 42)
  - American Law Institute 1988-2009, 4 folders (Box 42)
  - Symposium on Schools, Values, and the Courts, Yale Law School 1990 (Box 42)
  - Research Conference on Civil Justice Reform in the 1990s Institute of Judicial Administration, New York School of Law, 1993 (Box 42)
  - Harry S. Truman Scholarship Foundation, Selection Day Panel in Ann Arbor 1997-1998 (Box 42)
  - Judicial Symposium on the Criminalization of Corporate Conduct, Northwestern Law Judicial Education Program 2009 (Box 42)